<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
    xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
	<channel>
<title>News</title><link>https://genos.bio/index.html</link><description>Hot News&#x21;</description><dc:language>en</dc:language><language>en</language><dc:creator>GENOS</dc:creator><dc:rights>&#xa9; 2023 GENOS LLC</dc:rights><dc:date>2025-02-17T11:11:11-04:00</dc:date><admin:generatorAgent rdf:resource="http://www.realmacsoftware.com/" />
<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
<sy:updateBase>2000-01-01T12:00+00:00</sy:updateBase>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 5 Dec 2023 07:20:00 -0400</lastBuildDate><item><title>GENOS Launches Digital Contracting Platform to Enhance Bioinformatics Service Procurement</title><dc:creator>GENOS</dc:creator><category>Press</category><dc:date>2025-02-17T11:11:11-04:00</dc:date><link>https://genos.bio/news/files/GENOS-Launches-Digital-Contracting-Platform-to-Enhance-Bioinformatics-Service-Procurement.html#unique-entry-id-5</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://genos.bio/news/files/GENOS-Launches-Digital-Contracting-Platform-to-Enhance-Bioinformatics-Service-Procurement.html#unique-entry-id-5</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[SAN JUAN, PUERTO RICO &ndash;&nbsp;GENOS LLC, a computational biology and full-service bioinformatics contract research organization (CRO), announces the launch of its Digital Contract Procurement Platform, a system designed to expedite bioinformatics service requests, providing a single source of truth (SSOT) for enabling contract tracking and sharing between scientists, research teams and biotech companies. <br />]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>GENOS selected for Parallel18&#x2019;s pre18 program to strengthen market entry and expand operations.</title><dc:creator>GENOS</dc:creator><category>Press</category><dc:date>2024-12-18T07:00:00-04:00</dc:date><link>https://genos.bio/news/files/GENOS-selected-parallel18-pre18-strengthen-market-entry-expand-operations.html#unique-entry-id-4</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://genos.bio/news/files/GENOS-selected-parallel18-pre18-strengthen-market-entry-expand-operations.html#unique-entry-id-4</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[SAN JUAN, PUERTO RICO &ndash; GENOS LLC, a bioinformatics contract research organization (CRO), has been selected for the prestigious pre18 program by Parallel18, receiving a $25,000 equity-free grant and mentorship to strengthen its market entry in Puerto Rico and U.S. biotech hubs. As the only pure-play computational biology company in Puerto Rico, GENOS delivers tailored solutions in Omics Data, Molecular Dynamics, and Translational Studies, supporting local R&D teams and streamlining complex data workflows. This milestone highlights GENOS&rsquo; commitment to deploying scalable and productized bioinformatics services.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>GENOS to participate in the BioLeap Accelerator Program&#x27;s Inaugural Cohort</title><dc:creator>GENOS</dc:creator><category>Press</category><dc:date>2024-04-22T07:00:00-04:00</dc:date><link>https://genos.bio/news/files/genos-participate-bioleap-accelerator-puerto-rico.html#unique-entry-id-3</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://genos.bio/news/files/genos-participate-bioleap-accelerator-puerto-rico.html#unique-entry-id-3</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[SAN JUAN, PUERTO RICO &ndash; GENOS LLC, one of Ozcorp Scientific's recently debuted portfolio companies, has been selected to join the inaugural cohort of the BioLeap Life Science Startup Accelerator Program.  GENOS is a bioinformatics-as-a-service company providing innovative solutions to streamline research and development processes in life sciences. BioLeap is a program supported by the Build to Scale Program of the U.S. Economic Development Administration and managed by Parallel18 and the Puerto Rico Science, Technology & Research Trust. ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Ozcorp Scientific Unveils GENOS to Propel Biotechnology Research Through Tailored Bioinformatics Services  </title><dc:creator>GENOS</dc:creator><category>Press</category><dc:date>2024-04-18T07:00:00-04:00</dc:date><link>https://genos.bio/news/files/ozcorp-unveils-genos-bioinformatics-from-stealth.html#unique-entry-id-0</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://genos.bio/news/files/ozcorp-unveils-genos-bioinformatics-from-stealth.html#unique-entry-id-0</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[SAN JUAN, PUERTO RICO &ndash; Ozcorp Scientific, a biotech venture studio, proudly announces the official emergence of GENOS LLC, marking its decisive step out of stealth-mode and into the limelight of pioneering bioinformatics solutions. Spearheaded by Dr. Osvaldo D. Rivera, a Bioinformatics Scientist and Cancer Cell Biologist, GENOS aims to revolutionize the landscape of bioinformatics services by providing accessible solutions to investigator's most complex projects and biological data hurdles. GENOS is positioned strategically within Puerto Rico, a recently designated Tech Hub to spur American innovation in biotechnologies, biopharmaceuticals and medical device manufacturing.]]></content:encoded></item></channel>
</rss>